##### **LEARN MORE**

G2 Privacy Policy
=================

_Last updated on July 26, 2024._

This Privacy Policy describes our policies on the collection, use, and disclosure of information about you in connection with your use of our services, including those offered through the G2 website ([www.g2.com](http://www.g2.com/) and any subdomains) (“Site”) and communications (e.g., emails, phone calls, and texts) (collectively, “Service”). The terms “we”, “us”, “our” and “G2” refer to: (i) G2.com, Inc., a Delaware corporation with its headquarters in Chicago, Illinois. When you use the Service, you consent to our collection, use, and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy, our [Terms of Use](https://www.g2.com/terms-of-use) and our [Community Guidelines](https://www.g2.com/static/community_guidelines).

This Privacy Policy does not cover any information that you make publicly available through the Service or your use of any of G2’s paid products, nor does it cover G2’s employees, former employees or job applicants and prospects.

1\. About G2
------------

G2 offers a public website where you can search for and share information about technology products, services and providers, communicate with Site users, contribute reviews of technology products and services, and connect with software providers.

2\. Information We Collect and How We Use It
--------------------------------------------

We receive, store, and process certain types of personal information about you from your use of the Service, automatic data collection, and from certain third parties.

* * *

#### What Categories and Types of Information We Collect

We collect, transmit and store various categories of your personal information in connection with the Service. Over the last 12 months, we have collected the following categories of personal information:

| Category | Examples |
| --- | --- |
| Identifiers | First name, last name, email address |
| Commercial Information | Records of software products and/or services purchased, obtained or considered |
| Internet or other electronic network or device activity information | Search history, information on interactions with a website, application, or advertisement |
| Geolocation Data | Physical location, generally |
| Audio and visual information | Video reviews of software |
| Professional or employment information | Current or past employment, job title, employer name |
| Inferences | Activity on the Site to infer interest in certain products and categories |
| Sensitive personal information | Account login and password information |
| Browser | IP address, screen resolution, browser version/identity, browser language, local timezone |

G2 has not collected and does not plan to collect characteristics of protected classifications under applicable laws, biometric information, education information; and sensitive personal information other than account logins and encrypted passwords. Although neither required nor recommended, it is your choice to provide any of the foregoing information in connection with the Service and to make that information public.

When you use services such as Monty, G2’s AI-powered software buying assistant, G2 may store your chat logs with Monty for the purpose of gathering feedback about Monty and improving our products and services.

Please do not post on the Site or add to your account any personal data that you would not want to be publicly available.

* * *

#### Categories of Sources from Which We Collect Personal Information

We receive your personal information from any one or more of the following sources:

* _Directly from you._ When you visit the Site, log-in as a registered user, or provide your information in a form on the Site, we will collect and store that information.
* _Indirectly from you._ When you navigate and interact with the Site, some information is automatically collected by cookies and similar technologies. Not all information collected may be personal information, and some cookies are necessary to operationalize or maintain the Site or use different functionalities of the Site. The personal information collected may include information about your computer and internet connection, like IP address, operating system, and browser type. For more information about the cookies we use, see our [Cookie Policy](https://www.g2.com/cookie-policy).
* _From Social Media Networks._ When you use a social network login to access the Site, you will share certain personal information from your social media account with us. For example, if you connect to the Site through your LinkedIn account, we will receive and store your LinkedIn profile information and LinkedIn connections.
* _From Other Sources._ We also may periodically obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from affiliated entities, business partners, and other independent third-party sources and add it to other information about you. For example, if you visit the Site by “clicking-through” from a site operated by one of our business partners and you have registered with that partner, then information about you that you have provided to that partner may be shared with us.

* * *

#### Why We Use Your Personal Information

We may use personal information as permitted by law, for the following business purposes:

* _To provide the Service and various functions of the Service._ When you create an account on the Site, we store and use the information you provide during that process. This may include your first and last name, email address, the company you work for, and any other information you may provide during the account creation process. We may, if you consent, publicly display your first name and last initial, as well as any other photo or content you supply as part of your account profile. We also store and use any preferences you provide to personalize your user experience, including the types of software services and products that you use. Any reviews or other content that you submit to the Site are intended for public display and are therefore viewable by the public, including but not limited to your first name and last initial, and photos associated with your account. You can limit the public nature of some of this information in your account settings.
    * _For this business purpose, we may use these categories of information:_ identifiers, commercial information, internet or other electronic network or device activity information, geolocation data, audio and visual information, professional or employment information, inferences, sensitive personal information.
* _To fulfill any contact requests you make on the Site._ When you request additional information on a certain third-party service or product listed on the Site, we will use the information you provide to connect you with the provider of that service or product.
    * _For this business purpose, we may use these categories of information:_ identifiers, professional or employment information.

* _To engage in research and analysis related to the Site._ We store and use information to identify and fix errors, understand how visitors use the Site, research and test different features, and analyze how visitors arrive at and use the Site.
    * _For this business purpose, we may use these categories of information:_ identifiers, commercial information, internet or other electronic network or device activity information, geolocation data, professional or employment information, inferences, browser.
* _To personalize your experience._ We store and use information provided by you, such as the software products and services you use or have used, or are researching on the Site, to personalize and make recommendations to you based on your provided information.
    * _For this business purpose, we may use these categories of information_: identifiers, commercial information, internet or other electronic network or device activity information, geolocation data, browser.
* _To improve and understand usage of the Site._ We store and use information about your use of the Site, such as your search activity, pages viewed, and the date, time and duration of your visits, to understand and improve usage of the Site.
    * _For this business purpose, we may use these categories of information_: identifiers, commercial information, internet or other electronic network or device activity information, geolocation data, professional or employment information.
* _To provide feedback to third party businesses that are listed on the Site._ We store and use information about you or provided by you to assist our business partners in understanding their potential customers or current users.
    * _For this business purpose, we may use these categories of information_: identifiers, commercial information, audio and visual information, professional or employment information, inferences.
* _To enhance the security of the Service._ We store and use information to ensure the security of the Service. For example, we use the information collected by certain cookies to determine if you are logged in and to detect unauthorized access to your account.
    * _For this business purpose, we may use these categories of information_: identifiers, internet or other electronic network or device activity information, geolocation data.
* _To send you emails about G2's products and services._ We use your email address to send informational and marketing emails to you about new products and services, or updates to existing products or services. We may also contact you regarding feedback you provide us, or to learn more about your experience using the Site. Where appropriate, G2 will only do this with your consent.
    * _For this business purpose, we may use these categories of information_: identifiers, internet or other electronic network or device activity information, geolocation data.
* _To serve you offsite advertisements, including targeted advertising._ We may serve advertisements for G2 products and services to you through our advertising partners, based on information you provide during your site visit. Where appropriate, G2 will only do this with your consent. To check your settings, please review your [cookie preferences](#).
    * _For this business purpose, we may use these categories of information_: identifiers, commercial information, professional or employment information, internet or other electronic network or device activity information, browser.
* _To comply with legal obligations._ We use and share your personal information as necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process; we also may use and share your personal information to establish or exercise our legal rights, to defend against legal claims, or as otherwise required by law. We may use and share your personal information when we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal or suspected illegal activities; to protect and defend the rights, property, or safety of G2, the Site visitors and registered users, our licensees, and others.
    * _For this business purpose, we may use these categories of information_: identifiers, commercial information, internet or other electronic network or device activity information, geolocation data, audio and visual information, professional or employment information, inferences, sensitive personal information.
* _In connection with a corporate transaction._ We may use and share your personal information in connection with a corporate transaction, such as a divestiture, investment, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy.
    * _For this business purpose, we may use these categories of information_: identifiers, commercial information, internet or other electronic network or device activity information, geolocation data, audio and visual information, professional or employment information, inferences, sensitive personal information.

#### How We Share Your Information with Others

G2 may share your information with providers of products and services listed on the Site, our business partners, our service providers, social media networks, our affiliates, and any other third parties whom you authorize us to share your information with.

* _Sharing with providers of products and services listed on the Site._ When you expressly request to be contacted, we will share your personal information with the provider of the software product or service with whom you have asked to be connected, in order to fulfill your request. In fulfilling your request, we will provide the following personal information, to the extent you provide it:
    * First and last name;
    * Email address;
    * Phone number;
    * Employer information; and
    * General location information, at the state or country level.
* _Sharing your content._ When you leave a review on the Site, unattributed or not, that review and any personal information you have associated with that review, may be shared. This information may be displayed publicly on other social media sites, third-party software marketplaces, the providers of software products and services listed on the Site, and the operators of other publicly-available websites, platforms, or mobile apps that we have authorized to share this content through their websites, social media sites, platforms, mobile apps, or other marketing materials, such as slide decks or case studies. In sharing your content, we will share your personal information, to the extent you provide it, including:
    * First name, last initial;
    * Email address;
    * Profile picture associated with your G2 account;
    * Job title; and
    * Employer.
* _Sharing with our service providers._ G2 uses third party service providers to support or provide services for us in connection with the Site, such as hosting, security and fraud prevention, technical and user support, tracking and reporting usage of the Site, marketing, and other functions. We share your personal information with them as necessary to perform tasks on our behalf. The information that we share can include any of the categories identified in section 2 of this Privacy Policy.
* _Sharing with social networks._ If you sign in to your G2 account using a social network like LinkedIn or Facebook, we may share information about your activity or any content you post on the Site with the relevant social network. For example, if you write a review on the Site and elect to post that review on social media, we will share personal information you have provided in connection with that review to the relevant social network.
* _Sharing with our affiliates._ We share your personal information with our affiliates and require them to abide by this Privacy Policy. If another company were to acquire G2, or all or substantially all of our assets, that company would then possess any personal information G2 has about you, and will collect, use, and disclose that information solely as described in this Privacy Policy. The information that we share can include any of the categories identified in Section 2 of this Privacy Policy.

G2 may receive monetary or other valuable consideration for sharing your personal information when you submit a request to be contacted by a provider on the Site, or when you leave a review on the Site that we share with our clients. We do not share personal information with any other third parties. The personal information that is shared includes your first and last name, and email. Any other information you submit with your request or review will also be shared. G2 also, in limited circumstances, shares personal information with cross-context advertising partners.

Where G2 sells or shares your personal information, we do so to promote our products and services across platforms; to allow our clients to display your reviews on their sites; and to provide clients with meaningful insight into their competitive landscape.

G2 has not sold any other personal information for any other purpose in the last 12 months. G2 does not sell sensitive personal information, and the sensitive personal information that we collect is limited to your account login information and password.

3\. Cookies, Analytics, and Other Tracking Technologies
-------------------------------------------------------

#### Cookies and Tracking Technology

We want you to be aware that certain online tools exist to help us serve and recognize you when you visit the Site. We receive and store certain types of information when you visit the Site. When you access the Site, we (including companies we work with) may place small data files on your computer or other device. These data files may be web beacons, cookies, clear gifs, pixel tags, e-tags, flash cookies, log files, or other local storage provided by your browser or associated applications. These tracking technologies, which are often referred to collectively as cookies, allow us to understand how users navigate to and around the Site, view different pages, access content and request services. We may use them, for example, to keep track of your preferences and profile information and collect general usage and volume statistical information. If you want to remove or block cookies, you may be able to update your browser settings. For more information about our use of cookies, and to adjust your cookie preferences on the Site, please review our [Cookie Policy](https://www.g2.com/cookie-policy). You can also find instructions on how to manage cookies on different types of web browsers at [All About Cookies](https://allaboutcookies.org/). 

#### Do Not Track Signals

G2 does not currently respond to Do-Not-Track signals, although we do respond to the Global Privacy Control (GPC). You may adjust your preferences for certain tracking, for example, by disabling cookies or using ‘private’ or ‘incognito’ browsing modes. Learn more in our [Cookie Policy](https://www.g2.com/cookie-policy).

4\. Reviews and Other Content Published on the Site
---------------------------------------------------

If you leave a review on the Site, or participate on a discussion board, your review(s) or comments will be publicly available on and off of the Site. Other users may be able to identify you, or associate you with your account, if you include personal information in the content you post publicly. You can reduce the risk of being personally identified by using the Service anonymously. Please also note that the messages you send or receive using the Service are only private to the extent that both you and the recipient(s) of your messages keep them private. For example, if you send a message to another user, that user may choose to publicly post it. We may access, review, and disclose such messages in connection with investigations related to use of the Service, as well as our efforts to improve the Service.

Submitting reviews and comments is entirely voluntary. By submitting reviews and comments, you grant G2 an authorization to publicly share them and sub-license the content according to our [Terms of Use](https://www.g2.com/terms-of-use). This means that we can authorize the providers of software products and services to share this content through their websites, social media sites, or other marketing materials, such as slide decks or case studies, and/or the operators of other publicly-available websites, social media sites, platforms, or mobile apps to republish this content.

If you posted an attributed review under your name, you can change your mind later, and we will anonymize or delete it. However, please understand that we cannot guarantee others did not store the personal information prior to the change, by printing or downloading the original post.

5\. Your Data Privacy Rights
----------------------------

Depending on where you are located and/or live, you may exercise certain data privacy rights, and G2 will facilitate the exercise of those rights.

* * *

#### European Privacy Rights

If you are a resident or are otherwise located in the European Union ("EU") or the United Kingdom ("UK"), this section provides additional details about the personal data we collect about you, and your rights granted by the EU and UK General Data Protection Regulations, as applicable (“GDPR”).

Subject to certain limitations, the GDPR provides you the following privacy rights:

* _Transparency and the right to information._ Through this Privacy Policy we explain how we use and share your personal information. However, if you have questions or concerns you can contact us at privacy \[at\] g2.com.
* _Right of access, objection, restriction of processing, correction, erasure, and portability._ You can make a request to access, object, restrict, correct, erase, or transfer any of your personal information. You also have the right to withdraw your consent when we process your personal information based on your consent.
* _Right to opt-out from direct marketing._ You have the right to opt-out from receiving marketing materials from us by following the opt-out instructions in our commercial emails, by contacting us, or by adjusting your preferences under your profile details on the Site. Please note that we reserve the right to send you other communications, including transactional emails, service announcements and administrative messages relating to your G2 account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.
* _Right not to be subject to an automated decision, including profiling._ We do not make automated decisions using your personal data that may negatively impact you. We use cookies and similar technologies on the Site to personalize your experience on the Site and recommend software products and services that may be of interest to you. For additional information or to opt-out see our [Cookie Policy](https://www.g2.com/cookie-policy).
* _Right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority._ If you consider that the processing of your personal information infringes your GDPR privacy rights, you have the right to [lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority](https://ec.europa.eu/newsroom/article29/items/612080), in the member state of your habitual residence, place of work, or place of the alleged infringement. For users located in the UK, you can [contact the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO)](https://ico.org.uk/global/contact-us/).

If you would like to submit a request to G2 to exercise your EU or UK privacy rights under the GDPR, you may do so either by submitting a request through our [privacy rights form](https://www.g2.com/privacy-request), or by emailing privacy \[at\] g2.com with your request.

#### Legal Basis for Processing (EEA, Switzerland and United Kingdom only)

Our legal basis for collecting and using your personal information will depend on the type of information and the context in which we collect it.

However, we will normally collect personal information from you only in the following circumstances:

* We have your express consent to do so;
* We need the personal data to perform a contract with you; or
* Processing is in our legitimate interests and is not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms.

In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect personal information from you to protect your vital interests or those of another person (for example, to prevent, investigate or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with the Site or to comply with legal obligations).

If we ask you to provide personal information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contract with you, we will identify such basis for processing at the relevant time and let you know if the provision of your personal information is mandatory or not (as well as the possible consequences associated with not providing such information).

If we collect and use your personal information in reliance on our legitimate interests (or those of any third party), this interest will typically be to operate the Site, communicate with you in relation to your account or the Site, to solicit information from you, including through surveys, to share aggregated information with providers of listed products or services and other licensees of our research and report offerings, to measure interest in and improve our offerings and Site, to engage in marketing activities, and to otherwise customize your experience with G2.

If you have questions about or need further information concerning the legal basis on which we collect and use your personal information, please contact us at privacy \[at\] g2.com.

* * *

#### California Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of California, this section provides additional details about the personal information we collect about you, and your rights under the California Consumer Privacy Act ("CCPA") and California Privacy Rights Act ("CPRA").

Subject to certain limitations, the CCPA and CPRA provide you the right to request:

* That we provide you access to details on the categories or specific pieces of personal information we collect and/or sell (including how we use and disclose this information, to whom we may sell it);
* That we delete any of your personal information;
* That we correct any inaccuracies in your personal information;
* To opt out of any "sale" or "sharing" of your personal information that may occur, including sensitive personal information; and
* To not be discriminated against for exercising any of the above rights.

Please note that G2 does not collect sensitive personal information other than account login and password from its users.

If you would like to submit a request to exercise your California privacy rights, you may do so either by submitting a request through our [privacy rights form](https://www.g2.com/privacy-request), or by emailing privacy \[at\] g2.com with your request. We will verify your request using information associated with your account, including your email. Further identification may be required. You may also designate an authorized agent to act on your behalf.

Please note that G2 may retain a record of your request to delete your personal information.

You have the right to opt out of the sale or sharing of your personal information, including for the purpose of cross-context behavioral advertising. To opt out of cross-context behavioral advertising, please activate the "Do Not Sell" option in your [cookie preferences](#). To opt out of other kinds of sale or sharing, please visit our [opt-out form](https://www.g2.com/privacy-request).

As of July 2023, G2 does not sell, share, or otherwise make available for commercial purposes the personal data of 10 million or more California consumers.

G2 also responds to enabled Global Privacy Control ("GPC") browser settings. By enabling the GPC in a supported browser, your activity on that browser will be automatically opted out of the sale and sharing of your personal information through cookies.

_Notice of Financial Incentive:_ G2 may offer you a gift card in exchange for a review (an "incentivized review"). We collect the same categories of personal information disclosed in Section 2 for incentivized and unincentivized reviews, and your personal information is subject to this Privacy Policy in the same way. Completing an incentivized review is optional.

Please note that reviews must meet our [Community Guidelines](https://www.g2.com/static/community_guidelines) to qualify for a financial incentive.

_Shine The Light._ If you are a California resident, this section applies to you. The California Shine the Light law (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.83) permits residents of California to request certain details about how their information is shared with third parties for the third-parties’ direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please contact us at privacy \[at\] g2.com, and include “CA Shine the Light” in the subject line of your email.

* * *

#### Nevada Privacy Rights

Under Nevada law (SB 220), Nevada residents are permitted to opt-out of the sale of certain kinds of personal information. The term "sale" as used in the foregoing sentence means the transfer of your personal information to third parties for monetary consideration so the third parties can then re-sell or license the sold personal information. If you are a Nevada resident and wish to obtain information about our compliance with Nevada law, or opt out of the sale of your personal information, please contact us at privacy \[at\] g2.com.

* * *

#### Virginia Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of Virginia, this section provides information about your privacy rights under the Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act ("VCDPA").

Subject to certain limitations, the VCDPA affords you the following rights:

* To confirm whether we are processing your personal information, and to access that personal information;
* To receive your personal information in a portable and readily usable format;
* To correct inaccuracies in your personal information;
* To delete your personal information;
* To opt out of the processing of your personal information for targeted advertising, sale to third parties, or profiling where there is a legal or similarly significant effect on you.

You may exercise the rights to access, correct, delete or opt out of sale by visiting our self-service [privacy rights form.](https://www.g2.com/privacy-request) To opt out of targeted advertising, please adjust your [cookie preferences](#). You can also email privacy \[at\] g2.com for assistance with exercising your rights.

If G2 declines your request for any reason, we will notify you. You can appeal this decision by contacting privacy \[at\] g2.com.

Please note that G2 does not collect your sensitive personal information as defined by VCDPA.

* * *

#### Colorado Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of Colorado, this section provides information about your privacy rights under the Colorado Privacy Act ("CPA").

Subject to certain limitations, the CPA affords you the following rights:

* The right to opt out of targeted advertising, which you can do by adjusting your [cookie preferences](#);
* The right of access to the personal information we hold about you;
* The right to correction of any inaccurate data we hold about you;
* The right to deletion of your personal information;
* The right to opt out of the sale of your personal data; and
* The right to data portability, that is to access your personal information in a commonly used electronic format.

You may exercise these rights by visiting our self-service [privacy rights form](https://www.g2.com/privacy-request). You can also email privacy \[at\] g2.com for assistance with exercising your rights.

If G2 declines your request for any reason, we will notify you. You can appeal this decision by contacting privacy \[at\] g2.com.

Please note that G2 does not collect your sensitive personal information as defined by CPA.

* * *

#### Connecticut Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of Connecticut, this section provides information about your privacy rights under the Connecticut Data Privacy Act ("CTDPA").

Subject to certain limitations, the CTDPA affords you the following rights:

* To confirm whether we are processing your personal data, and to access said data;
* To correct inaccuracies in your personal data;
* To delete personal data that we collect from or obtain about you;
* To obtain a copy of your personal data in a portable and readily usable format; and
* To opt out of the processing of personal data for targeted advertising, the sale of personal data, or profiling where an automated decision produces a significant effect on you.

You may exercise the rights to access, correct, delete or opt out of sale by visiting our self-service [privacy rights form.](https://www.g2.com/privacy-request) To opt out of targeted advertising, please adjust your [cookie preferences](#). You can also email privacy \[at\] g2.com for assistance with exercising your rights.

Please note that G2 does not engage in profiling or automated decision making in a way that could produce a legal or other significant effect to you. 

If G2 declines your request for any reason, we will notify you. You can appeal this decision by contacting privacy \[at\] g2.com. If you are unhappy with the outcome of your appeal, you have the right to [file a complaint](https://portal.ct.gov/AG/Common/Complaint-Form-Landing-page) with the Office of the Attorney General of Connecticut.

* * *

6\. Processing in the United States
-----------------------------------

If you are accessing the Site from outside the United States, please be aware that your personal information will be transferred to, stored, and processed in the United States where our servers are located and our central database is operated. The data protection laws of the United States may not be equivalent or as comprehensive as the data protection laws as those in your country.

Your personal information may be processed outside your jurisdiction, including in countries and jurisdictions that are not subject to an adequacy decision by the European Commission or your local legislature or regulator, and that may not provide for the same level of data protection as your jurisdiction. We ensure that the recipient of your personal information offers an adequate level of protection and security, for instance by entering into the appropriate agreements and, if required, standard contractual clauses or an alternative mechanism for the transfer of data as approved by the European Commission (Art. 46 GDPR) or other applicable regulators or legislators. Where required by applicable law, we will only share, transfer or store your personal information outside of your jurisdiction with your prior consent.

We will provide an individual opt-out or opt-in choice before we share your data with third parties other than our agents, or before we use it for a purpose other than which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized. To request to limit the use and disclosure of your personal information, please submit a written request to privacy \[at\] g2.com.

7\. Data Privacy Framework
--------------------------

G2.com, Inc., including G2 subsidiaries Advocately, Inc. and Siftery, LLC comply with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework program (EU-U.S. DPF), the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework program (Swiss-U.S. DPF) as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce.  G2 has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework Principles (EU-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from the European Union in reliance on the EU-U.S. DPF and from the United Kingdom (and Gibraltar) in reliance on the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF.  G2 has certified to the U.S. Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework program Principles (Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles) with regard to the processing of personal data received from Switzerland in reliance on the Swiss-U.S. DPF.  If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the EU-U.S. DPF Principles and/or the Swiss-U.S. DPF Principles, the Principles shall govern.  To learn more about the Data Privacy Framework (DPF) program, and to view our certification, please visit the [Data Privacy Framework website](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/).

In compliance with the EU-US Data Privacy Framework Principles, G2 commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information transferred to the United States pursuant to the DPF Principles.  European Union, Swiss and United Kingdom individuals with DPF inquiries or complaints should first contact G2 at privacy \[at\] g2.com.

G2 has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the DPF Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, Data Privacy Framework Services, operated by BBB National Programs. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit the [BBB website](https://bbbprograms.org/programs/all-programs/dpf-consumers/ProcessForConsumers) for more information and to file a complaint. This service is provided free of charge to you.

If your  DPF complaint cannot be resolved through the above channels, under certain conditions, you may invoke [binding arbitration](https://www.dataprivacyframework.gov/s/article/G-Arbitration-Procedures-dpf?tabset-35584=2) for some residual claims not resolved by other redress mechanisms. With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Data Privacy Framework.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Data Privacy Framework, the Federal Trade Commission has jurisdiction over G2’s compliance with the EU-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (EU-U.S. DPF), the UK Extension to the EU-U.S. DPF, and the Swiss-U.S. Data Privacy Framework (Swiss-U.S. DPF).

Pursuant to the Data Privacy Framework, G2 may be required to disclose personal information in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

G2’s accountability for personal data that it receives in the United States under the Data Privacy Framework and subsequent onward transfers to a third party is described in the Data Privacy Framework Principles. In particular, G2 remains responsible and liable under the Data Privacy Framework Principles if third-party agents that it engages to process the personal data on its behalf do so in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, except where G2 is not responsible for the events giving rise to the damage.

8\. Security
------------

We have implemented appropriate administrative, technical, and physical security procedures to help protect your personal information.

For example, only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information that you do not publish on the Site, and they only may do so for permitted business functions. Our security and privacy policies are periodically reviewed and enhanced as necessary, and only authorized personnel have access to personal information that you have not published on the Site. In addition, we use encryption when transmitting your personal information between your system and ours, and we, together with our partners, employ firewalls and intrusion detection systems to help prevent unauthorized persons from gaining access to your non-public information.

Please bear in mind that submission of information over the Internet is never entirely secure. We cannot guarantee the security of information you submit via the Site while it is in transit over the Internet, and any such submission is at your own risk.

9\. This Site is Not Intended for Children
------------------------------------------

The Site is a general audience site and does not offer services directed to individuals under 18 years of age.

No one under the age of 18 may provide any information to or on the Site. We do not knowingly collect or share personal information from individuals under 18.

If you are under 18, do not use or provide any information on the Site or on or through any of its features, do not register on the Site, use any of the interactive or comment features of the Site, or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, or any screen name or user name you may use. Should an individual whom we know to be under the age of 18 send personal information to us, we will delete or destroy such information as soon as reasonably possible. If you believe we might have this type of information, please contact us.

10\. How Long We Keep Personal Information
------------------------------------------

G2 retains your personal information for as long as necessary to provide our services or during the period in which we have an ongoing legitimate business interest, to prevent, investigate, or identify possible wrongdoing in connection with the Site or to comply with legal obligations. With respect to personal information that has been collected using cookies and similar tracing technologies, you can view retention periods in our [Cookie Policy](https://www.g2.com/cookie-policy), as well as adjust and/or disable certain tracking. Information that you submit through your user profile is retained for the lifetime of your account with us. Please note that software product and service providers listed on the Site cannot remove their profile page, ratings, or reviews by closing their accounts.

11\. Updates to Our Privacy Policy
----------------------------------

This Privacy Policy is current as of the last updated date set forth above. G2 may, in its sole and absolute discretion, update this Privacy Policy from time to time. G2 will post its updated Privacy Policy to the Site. You acknowledge that your continued use of the Site and/or continued provision of personal information to G2 after we publish an updated Privacy Policy will be considered acceptance of any changes to this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy for any changes. You can see when this Privacy Policy was last updated by checking the “last updated” date displayed at the top of this Privacy Policy.

12\. Contact Us
---------------

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or want to communicate with our Data Protection Officer, please contact us at privacy \[at\] g2.com.

Or

G2.com, Inc.  
Attn: Privacy Team  
100 S. Wacker Dr., Suite 600  
Chicago, IL 60606 USA

Please provide your identification and contact details, including your email address used to register with the Site, and a complete explanation of your concern.
